logrocket.com 2019-08-25

# LogRocket: Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Thanks for visiting LogRocket. This privacy policy explains the what, how, and why of the personally identifying Information we collect when you visit the website located at www.logrocket.com (the “Site”) and when you use the LogRocket SaaS analytics software and services (“Services”) and includes Personal Information collected via email, SMS, telephone, WAP or other means. It also explains the specific ways we use and disclose that information. By using or accessing the Site or Services, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy, and you are consenting to our processing of your information as described below. 

### About LogRocket

LogRocket is a new type of developer tool. It’s like a DVR for web apps, recording literally everything that happens on your site. Instead of guessing why problems happen, you can replay sessions with bugs or user issues to quickly understand the root cause. 

LogRocket instruments the DOM to record the HTML and CSS on the page, recreating pixel-perfect videos of even the most complex single page apps. 

In addition, LogRocket records console logs, JavaScript errors, stacktraces, network requests/responses with headers + bodies, browser metadata, and custom logs. It also has deep integrations with libraries like React, Redux, and Angular to log actions and application state. 

### Definitions

Getting a few definitions out of the way should help you better understand this policy. When we say we, us, our or LogRocket, we're referring to LogRocket, a Delaware corporation. LogRocket Customer refers to any customer that has entered into an agreement with LogRocket to use the LogRocket Services on its Site. Personal Information means all information relating to a person that identifies such person or could reasonably be used to identify such person, including but not limited to, as first and last name, home address, billing address, or other physical address, email address, telephone number and Sensitive Data, if any. User refers to a visitor to a website that uses the LogRocket Services or a client of a LogRocket Customer. Visitor refers to anyone accessing the LogRocket Site. 

### Information Collected

#### Information Collected from LogRocket Visitors

If you are a Visitor, LogRocket collects information on your use of our Site, such as pages visited, links clicked, non-sensitive text entered, and mouse movements, as well as information more commonly collected such as the referring URL, browser, operating system, cookie information, and Internet Service Provider (“Usage Data”). LogRocket’s purpose in collecting Usage Information is to better understand how LogRocket’s Visitors use the Site. LogRocket does not use the Usage Information to identify its Visitors and does not disclose the Usage Information other than under the circumstances described in this Privacy Policy. 

As a Visitor, LogRocket collects potentially personally identifying information like Internet Protocol (or “IP”) addresses (“Potential PII”). Also, you may choose to interact with the Site that results in your providing Personal Information to LogRocket, such as giving us your name, email address, user name and password when signing up for a free trial of the Services or creating an account to post comments to the LogRocket blog or social media sites, etc. You should be aware that any information you provide in the LogRocket blog or social media areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. 

We only collect Personal Information that is reasonable or necessary to accomplish the purpose of your interaction with LogRocket as a Visitor. You may choose not to provide this information but you need to understand that as a result, you may not be able to engage in certain activities on the Site. Any Personal Information provided by you as a Visitor to the Site will be used only as described in this Privacy Policy and LogRocket’s Acceptable Use Policy. 

#### Information Collected from LogRocket Customers

If you are a Customer of LogRocket, when you signed up for the Services, you entered into an agreement with LogRocket to accept LogRocket’s terms of use of the Services, which includes the obligations in this Privacy Policy and our Acceptable Use Policy (“Agreement”). As part of your use of the Services, we collect the same information as that of a Visitor above and may ask you for additional information such as payment information, usage data in relation to the Services and other information we deem relevant for the purpose of providing the Services. LogRocket may use your information and data as agreed to in the Agreement and to: 

  * Process transactions between you and LogRocket.
  * Communicate with you about our Services, including sending you e-mail newsletters.
  * Let you know about changes to our policies and terms.
  * Provide support for the LogRocket Services.
  * Enhance or improve user experience, our Site, or LogRocket Services.
  * Monitor data to ensure that it complies with your contractual obligations to us.
  * Perform any other function that we believe in good faith is necessary to protect the security or proper functioning of our Site or the LogRocket Services.
  * With your prior consent, we may post your personal testimonials along with those of other satisfied customers on our Site in addition to other endorsements.

The information we collect from a Customer is disclosed only in accordance with the Agreement and this Privacy Policy and the Acceptable Use Policy. 

#### Information Collected from Visits to Websites that use LogRocket Services

For Users of a LogRocket Customer, LogRocket is acting as a service provider to the Customer for the LogRocket Services. LogRocket collects information on a User under the direction of its Customer, and has no direct relationship with the User whose information it processes. It is important to understand that when a User visits other websites that use the LogRocket Services, the LogRocket Customer’s privacy policy apply to that information collected instead of this Privacy Policy. LogRocket may use your information as permitted by the LogRocket Customer in accordance with its privacy policies. 

### Use of Your Personal Information

In the course of business, we may hire third party individuals and organizations to help us make the LogRocket Services better. These third parties include our web host provider, other SaaS providers, such as an email hosting service, payment processors or outside contractors we hire to perform maintenance or assist us in securing our website. We may also hire third parties to operate, maintain, repair, or otherwise improve or preserve our website or its underlying files or systems.

LogRocket may disclose Personal Information and Potential PII only to those of its employees and third party organizations that (1) need to know such information in order to process it on LogRocket’s behalf or to provide services as described above and (2) have agreed not to disclose it to any other parties without LogRocket’s consent. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using the Site and/or the Service, you consent to the transfer of information to such individuals and organizations in order to accomplish these purposes.

Before using or sharing your information with non-agent third parties in ways not discussed here or previously authorized by you, we will provide you Notice and an opportunity to control the further use or disclosure of your personal information.

LogRocket has potential liability in cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of EU and Swiss individuals received pursuant to the Privacy Shield Principles. 

If you are a registered user of the Service and have supplied your email address, LogRocket may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with LogRocket and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. LogRocket takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of Personal Information and Potential PII.

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the transferred business assets. If we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us or our assets may continue to use your Personal Information and Potential PII as set forth in this policy. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Site of any change in ownership or uses of your Personal Information and Potential IP, as well as any choices you may have regarding your Personal Information and Potential IP. 

We will also provide an EU or Swiss individual with opt-out or opt-in choice before we share their data with third parties other than our agents, or before we use it for a purpose other than which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized. 

To limit the use and disclosure of your personal information, please submit a written request to support@logrocket.com. 

### Release of Your Information for Legal Purposes

We may access or release Personal Information about you when required to do so in order to comply with any applicable, laws, regulations, subpoena or enforceable governmental or public authority request, including, to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We may also access or release Personal Information when we have a good faith believe that such access or release is reasonably necessary to (i) enforce applicable terms of service, including investigation of potential violations, (ii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (iii) respond to user support requests, or (iv) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam/malware prevention. 

### Right to Access, Edit, and Remove Your Information

You have a right to access personal information we hold about you. Whenever you use our Site or LogRocket Services, we strive to make sure that the Personal Information is correct. If that information is wrong, we give you ways to update it quickly or to delete it – unless we have to keep that information for legitimate business or legal purposes. 

When updating your Personal Information, we may ask you to verify your identity before making any changes. We may reject requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort (for example, developing a new system or fundamentally changing an existing practice), risk the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup systems). 

Where we can provide information access and correction, we will do so for free, except where it would require a disproportionate effort. Because we protect information from accidental or malicious destruction, even after information is deleted from the LogRocket Services, it may not be immediately deleted from LogRocket’s servers.

To request removal of your Personal Information from our Site, Services, blog or social media, contact us at support@logrocket.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your Personal Information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

If a User interacts with one of our Customers and the User seeks to access, or correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data or no longer wants to be contacted by one of our Customers, the User should direct its inquiry to the Customer because the Customer is the data controller. If the Customer requests LogRocket to remove the Personal Information, we will respond to their request within 30 days. 

### Security Measures

We take measures to enhance the security of our Site and the LogRocket Service. These measures include using SSL Certificates and two-factor authentication. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. No security measures are perfect and we cannot promise that the information about you will remain secure in all circumstances. 

### International Transfer

We store and process information about you on computers in the United States. Privacy laws local to our servers and computers will apply to information we store about you. 

### Do Not Track Signal

We treat the data of everyone who comes to our site in accordance with this Privacy Policy, whatever their Do Not Track setting. 

### Children

Our site is intended for a general audience and we do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13. 

### How LogRocket Collects Information

Cookies are small data files placed on your computer by the websites you visit and the emails you read and can be used to help recognize you when you return to a website, or when you visit other sites. We, or third party service providers, may use cookies to, among other things, measure activity, personalize your experience, remember your viewing preferences, or track your status or progress when accessing our site. For some of these purposes, our cookies may be tied to Personal Information and/or Potential PII. In particular, the LogRocket Services use first-party cookies to maintain a coherent scope for a user session across multiple pages on a single website. These cookies do not track the same user across unrelated domains and, as described above, attempts to infer identity across domains is strictly prohibited.

Local Storage is a standard facility provided by HTML5-compliant browsers used to retain data on your computer across visits to the same website. We use local storage as a temporary holding area for user events that were observed locally but, due to the timing of a page unload, were unable to be transmitted as part of the user session. Return visits to the same website read and transmit events previously stored in local storage to complete previously recorded sessions.

This information may in the aggregate identify a User, however we will not identify a User as they browse the web if the User turns off cookies, as explained below.

LogRocket does not and will not ever attempt to identify the same person across disparate, unrelated domains. It is a violation of our Acceptable Use Policy for our customers to attempt to build multi-site user profiles for the intent of selling or exchanging lists of users or demographic information. 

### List of data Sub processors

Amazon Web Services, Inc - USA  
Google LLC - USA  
Redis Labs - USA  

### EU-US Privacy Shield

LogRocket complies with both the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework, as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland to the United States. LogRocket has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the policies in this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles will govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, LogRocket commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact LogRocket at: privacy@logrocket.com. 

LogRocket has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield Principles, to the BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers for more information and to file a complaint. The services of BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD are provided at no cost to you. 

Under certain limited conditions, if your complaint is not resolved through these channels, it may be possible for individuals to invoke binding arbitration before the Privacy Shield Panel to be created by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission. 

LogRocket is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). 

### Changes

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. When there are changes to this Privacy Policy, we will update this page. The date on the bottom will always indicate when we last made changes. If you are a visitor to this Site and disagree with the Privacy Policy, you should leave the Site and/or cancel your agreement with LogRocket. 

### What If I Have Questions or Concerns?

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy when using LogRocket, please send us a detailed message to support@logrocket.com. We will make every effort to address your concerns. 

**Last Updated:** May 3, 2018
